Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1989.0080
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IV: Administrative Records, undated, 1925-1991
  - Subseries A: Correspondence and Subject Files, 1955-1991
    - Legislative Electoral Action Program, 1985 (Box 178)
    - Legislative session, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Letters to the editor, undated (Box 193)
    - Letters to the editor, undated (Box 201)
    - Linkage, Ordinance Establishing a Neighborhood Policy, 1985 (Box 178)
    - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Labor Day statements, 1986-1987 (Box 192)
    - Laborsphere Game, undated (Box 195)
    - Long term care, 1988 (Box 192)
    - M.D. Health Plan, 1989 (Box 192)
    - MacBride Principle, 1986 (Box 178)
    - March for justice, Pittston, Greenwich, undated (Box 193)
    - Marshall, Ray, undated (Box 178)
    - Matchko, Madeline, Testimonial Golf Tournament for, undated (Box 197)
    - Medicare catastrophic coverage, undated (Box 193)
    - Merit system, 1985 (Box 178)
    - Metal Trades Council, undated (Box 193)
    - Mini-Conference on Organizational Innovation, undated (Box 193)
    - Minimum wage, undated (Box 193)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 27:, Folder 1278)
    - Miscellaneous—1982 election, undated (Box 196)
    - Miscellaneous letters, undated (Box 196)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, undated (Box 193)
    - N: miscellaneous, undated (Box 197)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens, undated (Box 193)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens, undated (Box 197)
    - National legislative issues, undated (Box 197)
    - Naugatuck Valley Project, 1986 (Box 178)
    - Naugatuck Valley Project, undated (Box 194)
    - Naugatuck Valley Project, undated (Box 197)
    - Naugatuck Valley Project, undated (Box 201)
    - News clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 178)
    - Nicaragua, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Northeast AFL-CIO Council: Health Care Conference, 1991 (Box 201)
      - Meeting in D.C., 1991
    - Northeast Utilities, undated (Box 178)
    - Occupational Health Clinics, undated (Box 194)
    - Occupational Health Clinics Advisory Committee (Box 201)
    - Occupational Medicine Program Proposal: Dr. Eileen Story, undated (Box 197)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union, undated
      - (O.P.E.I.U.) Local 376: Health and Welfare Records, undated
      - Audit reports, undated (Box 204)
      - Blue Cross/Blue Shield billings, undated (Box 204)
      - Bonding, undated (Box 204)
      - Bonding contract, undated (Box 204)
      - Boston Mutual, undated (Box 204)
        - Bills, undated (Box 204)
        - Correspondence, 1973-88; (2 folders) (Box 204)
        - Policy, undated (Box 204)
      - Bristol Savings Bank, undated (Box 204)
      - Finalized pension forms, undated (Box 204)
      - Financial reports, undated; (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - Insurance package for Trustees meeting, undated (Box 204)
      - I.R.S. forms, undated (Box 204)
      - Listing of employers, undated (Box 204)
      - Miscellaneous paid bills, undated (Box 204)
      - Notice to employees, undated (Box 204)
      - Notice to employers, undated (Box 204)
      - O.P.E.I.U. 376, undated (Box 204)
      - AFL-CIO & UAW: pension and welfare membership, undated (Box 204)
      - Financial statements, examples of, 1969-71 (Box 204)
      - Correspondence, welfare and pension, undated (Box 204)
      - Membership lists, undated (Box 204)
      - Office correspondence, undated (Box 204)
      - Old insurance, undated (Box 204)
      - Secretary's book, 1984-1989 (Box 204)
      - Pension and welfare agreements, undated (Box 204)
      - Welfare fund problem with embezzlement, undated (Box 204)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, undated (Box 204)
    - Olsen, John W.: President, undated (Box 197)
    - O'Neill, William (Governor), undated (Box 194)
    - O'Neill, William (Governor), undated; (2 folders) (Box 197)
    - OSHA, 1987 (Box 192)
    - Other State Federations, undated (Box 174)
    - Pay equity, 1985-1987 (Box 178)
    - Pay equity, 1974-1984 (Box 192)
    - Pay records of public employees, 1987 (Box 178)
    - Personnel, miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 27:, Folder 1279)
    - Petronella, Ronald (Commissioner), undated (Box 197)
    - Plant closings, 1985-1987 (Box 178)
    - Plumbers and Pipefitters Pension Fund Trustee, undated (Box 197)
    - Plumbers and Pipefitters Pension Fund Trustees, undated (Box 201)
    - Polygraph, undated (Box 178)
    - Preparation for Second Governors' Conference, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Press releases, 1987 (Box 178)
    - Press releases, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Private Industry Councils in Connecticut, undated (Box 197)
    - Private Right of Action, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Privatization, undated (Box 197)
    - Project 500, undated (Box 201)
    - Psychology, Industrial Applications Center, 1987 (Box 178)
    - Public Employee Conference, Atlantic City, 1991 (Box 201)
    - Public Employee Meeting, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Public relations, 1965 (Box 27:, Folder 1281)
    - Public Works, Department of, undated (Box 197)
    - Publications, 1967 (Box 27:, Folder 1280)
    - Rainbow Coalition, undated (Box 201)
    - ( A. Philip) Randolph Institute, 1988 (Box 192)
    - ( A. Philip) Randolph Institute (Box 194)
    - Red Cross, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Redistricting, undated (Box 201)
    - Regional Council Meeting, AFL-CIO, undated (Box 174)
    - Religion and Labor Conference, undated (Box 197)
    - Rhode Island Economic Development Plan, 1983 (Box 178)
    - Right to Work, 1985 (Box 178)
    - Right to Work, undated (Box 197)
    - Rourke, Joseph, undated (Box 201)
    - Rowland, John, undated (Box 197)
    - Sacred Heart University, undated (Box 197)
    - Sacred Heart University (Box 201)
    - School hours, 1982 (Box 178)
    - Secretary Treasurer, undated (Box 197)
    - Senate Committee on Business Opportunity, undated (Box 194)
    - Senators, U.S., undated (Box 194)
    - Service Employees International Union, undated (Box 201)
    - Shell boycott, 1986 (Box 178)
    - Shell boycott, undated (Box 197)
    - Slaiman, Donald—COPE Director, undated (Box 194)
    - Social Democrats, undated (Box 194)
    - Social Security, 1982 (Box 178)
    - Softball tournament and picnic, 1989 (Box 194)
    - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 178)
    - Solidarity Day, 1991 (Box 201)
    - South Africa, undated (Box 201)
    - Southeast Asia, trip to, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Staff meeting minutes, undated (Box 197)
    - Staff memoranda, 1988 (Box 191)
    - State Employee, undated (Box 178)
      - Issues, 1986 (Box 178)
      - Retirement, 1987 (Box 178)
      - Contracts, undated (Box 178)
      - Collective Bargaining, 1985 (Box 178)
      - Pension, 1988 (Box 192)
    - State Employee Bargaining Agreement Coalition (SEBAC), undated (Box 201)
    - State Government Liaison, Office of, undated (Box 194)
    - State Management Association of CT, Inc., 1986 (Box 178)
    - State Tax Coalition, 1990-91 (Box 201)
    - State Treasurer: testimonial, speeches, memos, undated (Box 197)
    - Summer School, 1989 (Box 194)
    - Summer School, 1990 (Box 197)
    - Summer school, 1991 (Box 201)
    - Sunday and holiday work, undated (Box 27:, Folder 1282)
    - Surveys of membership, undated (Box 201)
    - Tax Reform, Coalition on, 1989 (Box 194)
    - Teamsters, undated (Box 198)
    - Teleconference on National Legislation, 1991 (Box 201)
    - Television stations, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Television stations, undated (Box 197)
    - Testimonial: staff, undated (Box 197)
    - Testimonies, 1985-1987 (Box 179)
    - Tianti, Betty, Commissioner CT Dept. of Labor, undated (Box 194)
    - Tianti, Betty L., Commissioner of Labor, undated (Box 197)
    - Tianti, Betty L.; Scholarship Fund Raising Committee, undated (Box 194)
    - Tianti Scholarship, undated (Box 197)
    - Tianti Scholarship, undated (Box 201)
    - Transportation, 1987-1988 (Box 179)
    - Transportation, undated (Box 194)
    - U: miscellaneous, undated (Box 198)
    - UConn, 1986 (Box 179)
      - Health Center, 1985 (Box 179)
      - Institute for Social Inquiry, 1985 (Box 179)
      - Labor Education Center, 1984 (Box 179)
      - Labor Education Center, undated (Box 198)
    - Unemployment compensation, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Unemployment compensation, undated (Box 197)
    - Unemployment compensation, undated (Box 201)
    - U.S. Department of the Treasury: certificate to John Olson, undated (Box 201)
    - Union Yes, 1988 (Box 191)
    - United Labor Agency, 1987 (Box 179)
    - United Labor Agency, 1988; (2 fl) (Box 192)
    - United Labor Agency, 1989 (Box 194)
    - United Labor Agency, 1990 (Box 197)
    - United Labor Agency, 1991 (Box 201)
    - United Mine Workers (Pittston Strike Assistance), undated (Box 194)
    - United Seniors in Action, 1988 (Box 192)
    - United States Department of Labor, undated (Box 197)
    - United States House of Representatives, undated (Box 197)
    - United States savings bonds, undated (Box 198)
    - United States Senate, undated (Box 198)
    - United Way, 1988 (Box 192)
    - United Way, undated (Box 201)
    - United Way of S.E. Connecticut, undated (Box 194)
    - Unity 500, undated (Box 179)
    - University of Connecticut Labor Education Center (Box 194)
    - UConn Labor Education Center Advisory Committee, undated (Box 194)
    - University of Connecticut, Stamford: Area Advisory Committee, undated (Box 201)
    - Urban Affairs, Office of, undated (Box 194)
    - VDT, 1986 (Box 179)
    - Veterans Administration, undated (Box 192)
    - Veterans Hospital Study, 1987 (Box 192)
    - Video display tube information, 1984 (Box 192)
    - Vietnam Veterans of America, 1987 (Box 192)
    - VIP meetings, 1989 (Box 194)
    - Volunteers in Politics, 1985-1987; (3 fl.) (Box 179)
    - Voter registration, coalition, 1987 (Box 179)
    - Wages, prevailing rate of, undated (Box 198)
    - War in the Middle East, 1991 (Box 201)
    - Weicker, Lowell, undated (Box 194)
    - Windham Textile Museum, undated (Box 194)
    - Windham Textile Museum, undated (Box 198)
    - Women, 1986 (Box 179)
    - Women and Civil Rights, undated (Box 198)
    - Women, Permanent Commission on the status of, undated (Box 198)
    - Worker's Compensation, undated (Box 194)
    - Workers Compensation Commission, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Workers compensation: Division of Workers' Education, 1988 (Box 192)
    - Workers compensation rates, undated (Box 201)
    - Workers Education Division of Workers Compensation, undated (Box 194)
    - Workmen's Compensation Division of Worker Education, 1984 (Box 179)
    - Workshops, 1986-1987 (Box 179)
    - Workers compensation, undated (Box 198)
    - Workers Memorial Day, 1991 (Box 201)
    - Y: miscellaneous, undated (Box 198)
    - Youth Leadership Seminar, undated (Box 179)
    - Zolot, Norman Legal Counsel, undated (Box 194)
    - Zolot, Norman: Legal Counsel, undated (Box 198)
  - Subseries B: AFL-CIO [National], undated, 1960-1975
    - President, 1963-1975 (Box 27:, Folder 1283)
    - President, George Meany, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3427-3430)
    - President, Lane Kirkland, undated (Box 181)
    - President, Lane Kirkland, undated (Box 191)
    - President Lane Kirkland, undated (Box 193)
    - President Lane Kirkland, undated (Box 198)
    - President Lane Kirkland, undated (Box 203)
    - Secretary-Treasurer, 1964-1974 (Box 27:, Folder 1284)
    - Secretary-Treasurer, Thomas Donahue, undated (Box 181)
    - Secretary-Treasurer, Thomas Donahue, undated (Box 191)
    - Secretary-Treasurer, Thomas R. Donahue, undated (Box 193)
    - Secretary Treasurer, Thomas R. Donahue (Box 198)
    - Secretary Treasurer Thomas R. Donahue, undated (Box 203)
    - Coordinator, 1962-1974 (Box 27:, Folder 1285)
    - COPE, undated (Box 174)
    - COPE, undated (Box 191)
    - COPE: John Perkins, Director, undated (Box 193)
    - COPE, National John Perkins, undated (Box 198)
    - Departments
      - Building and Construction Trades Council, undated (Box 191)
      - Building and Construction Trades, undated (Box 198)
      - Building and Construction Trades, undated (Box 203)
      - Building trades, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3436)
      - Civil Rights, 1967, 1973 (Box 28:, Folder 1291)
      - Civil rights, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3437)
      - Community Services, 1970-1974 (Box 28:, Folder 1292)
      - Community services, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3438-3441)
      - Community Services, undated (Box 181)
      - Community Services, undated (Box 191)
      - Community Services, undated; (2 fl) (Box 193)
      - Community Services, undated (Box 198)
      - Community Services, undated (Box 203)
      - Education, 1962-1973 (Box 28:, Folder 1293-1295)
      - Education, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3442-3444)
      - Education, undated (Box 181)
      - Education, undated (Box 191)
      - Education, undated (Box 193)
      - Education, undated (Box 198)
      - Education, undated (Box 203)
      - Employee Benefits, undated (Box 203)
      - Food and beverage trades, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3445)
      - Housing and Urban Development, undated (Box 28:, Folder 1296)
      - Human resources, 1971-1982 (Box 118:, Folder 3446-3449)
      - Human Resources Development Institute, 1969-1973 (Box 28:, Folder 1297)
      - Industrial Union, 1964-1974 (Box 28:, Folder 1298)
      - Industrial union, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3450)
      - Industrial union, undated (Box 181)
      - Information, undated (Box 181)
      - International affairs, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3451)
      - International Affairs, undated (Box 181)
      - International Affairs, undated (Box 191)
      - International Affairs, undated (Box 198)
      - Investments, 1967-1974 (Box 28:, Folder 1299)
      - Labor Day, 1964-1965 (Box 28:, Folder 1307)
      - Labor Institute, George Meany Center, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3456)
      - Legislation, 1962-1975 (Box 28:, Folder 1300-1301)
      - Legislation, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3452-3455)
      - Legislation, undated (Box 193)
      - Legislation, undated (Box 198)
      - Legislation, undated (Box 203)
      - Legislation “Fact Sheet”, 1960-1966 (Box 29:, Folder 1302)
      - Legislative, undated (Box 181)
      - Legislative, undated (Box 191)
      - Maritime Trades, 1972 (Box 29:, Folder 1303)
      - Maritime trades, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3457)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3458)
      - National Mortgage Investment Trust, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3459)
      - News, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3460)
      - Occupational Safety and Social Security, undated (Box 181)
      - Occupational Safety and Health, undated (Box 198)
      - Occupational safety, Health and Social Security, undated (Box 193)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1965-1968 (Box 29:, Folder 1304)
      - Organization, 1967, 1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1305)
      - Organization and Field services, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3462-3463)
      - Organizational and Field Services, undated (Box 181)
      - Organization and field services, undated (Box 193)
      - Organization and Field Services, undated (Box 198)
      - Organization and Field Services, undated (Box 203)
      - OSHA, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3461)
      - Professional employees, undated (Box 193)
      - Professional Employees, undated (Box 203)
      - Public Affairs, undated (Box 181)
      - Public employees, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3464-3465)
      - Public Employees, undated (Box 181)
      - Public employees, undated (Box 191)
      - Public employees, undated (Box 193)
      - Public Employees, undated (Box 203)
      - Public Relations, 1968-1971 (Box 29:, Folder 1306)
      - Publications, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3466)
      - Research, 1968-1974 (Box 29:, Folder 1308)
      - Research, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3467-3468)
      - Research, undated (Box 181)
      - Research, undated (Box 191)
      - Research, undated (Box 193)
      - Research, undated (Box 198)
      - Research, undated (Box 203)
      - Social Security, 1963-1968 (Box 29:, Folder 1309-1311)
      - Social Security, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3469-3470)
      - Task Force for Burke-Harte Act, 1968-1973 (Box 29:, Folder 1312)
      - Union Label, undated (Box 203)
      - Union Label Service Trades, 1968-1973 (Box 29:, Folder 1313)
      - Union Label Service trades, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3471)
      - Union Label and service trades, undated (Box 193)
      - Union Label and Service Trades, undated (Box 198)
      - Urban Affairs, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3472)
    - Executive Council, 1958 (Box 27:, Folder 1286)
    - Executive Council, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3432-3435)
    - Executive Council>, undated (Box 181)
    - Executive Council, undated (Box 203)
    - Housing Investment Trust, undated (Box 181)
    - Housing Investment Trust, undated (Box 191)
    - Housing investment trust, undated (Box 193)
    - Housing Investment Trust, undated (Box 198)
    - Housing Investment Trust, undated (Box 203)
    - Human Resource Development Institute, undated (Box 193)
    - HRDI, undated (Box 191)
    - H.R.D.I., National, undated (Box 198)
    - ILCA, undated (Box 191)
    - Institute of Labor Communicators “Union Yes”, undated (Box 193)
    - Labor Institute for Public Affairs, undated (Box 181)
    - Labor Institute for Public Affairs, undated (Box 191)
    - Labor Institution of Public Affairs, undated (Box 198)
    - Matchko, Madelaine, National AFL-CIO COPE, undated (Box 198)
    - Meany Center, undated (Box 193)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 181)
    - Miscellany, undated (Box 193)
    - National Activities, undated (Box 174)
    - National AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1962-1968 (Box 28:, Folder 1287-1290)
      - Secretary-Treasurer, Lane Kirkland, undated (Box 118:, Folder 3431)
    - National COPE, undated (Box 181)
    - Northeast AFL-CIO, undated (Box 193)
    - Occupational Safety, Health and Social Security, undated (Box 191)
    - Organization and Field Services, undated (Box 191)
    - Political Education, John Perkins, Director, undated (Box 203)
    - Privileges Benefits Program, undated (Box 181)
    - Privileges Benefit Program, undated (Box 191)
    - Region VIII AFL-CIO, undated (Box 193)
    - State Government Liaison, Office of, undated (Box 198)
    - Union Benefits Program, undated (Box 198)
    - Union privilege, undated (Box 203)
  - Subseries C: Executive Board, undated, 1945-1987
    - Officers
      - President, John Driscoll, 1961-1962 (Box 29:, Folder 1314)
      - Driscoll, John J., President Emeritus, 1988 (Box 191)
      - Driscoll, John, President Emeritus (Box 193)
      - Olsen, John W., President, 1988 (Box 191)
      - Vice-President, Leonard Kershner, 1968 (Box 29:, Folder 1315)
      - Secretary-Treasurer, Joseph Bober, 1965-1967 (Box 29:, Folder 1316)
      - Williams, Barry R., Secretary-Treasurer, 1988 (Box 191)
      - Secretary, Harold Conroy, 1965-1969 (Box 29:, Folder 1317)
      - Director of Education, Ruth Greenberg, 1965 (Box 29:, Folder 1318)
      - Research Director, Keith Proudy, 1960-1962 (Box 29:, Folder 1319)
      - Applications, 1958 (Box 29:, Folder 1320)
      - Officers and members, 1959-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 1321-1327)
    - Affiliation Committee, undated (Box 193)
    - Bates, Matthew, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Building and Construction trade, undated (Box 193)
    - Christella, Frank, 1985 (Box 180)
    - CIO-CSIUC, Legislative Committee, 1946-1956 (Box 30:, Folder 1330-1335)
    - Council affiliates, 1965 (Box 29:, Folder 1328)
    - Executive Board, 1985-1987 (Box 180)
    - Executive Board, 1988 (Box 191)
    - Executive Board, undated (Box 193)
    - Executive Council, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3482-3490)
    - Executive Secretary, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3475)
    - Executive-Treasurer, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3476)
    - Financial Data, undated (Box 193)
    - Financial reports, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3504-3508)
    - Financial reports, 1988 (Box 191)
    - General Vice President, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3473-3474)
    - Meeting minutes, undated (Box 29:, Folder 1329)
      - News releases, undated (Box 193)
      - Newspaper, undated (Box 193)
    - Noonan, Mike, 1986 (Box 180)
    - Secretary-Treasurer, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3477)
    - Staff, undated (Box 193)
    - Staff Correspondence, undated (Box 120)
      - Frank Christello, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3478)
      - Roger Claymen, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3479-3480)
      - Chris Mueller, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3481)
    - Staff meeting minutes, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3491-3494)
    - Staff memoranda, undated (Box 120:, Folder 3495-3503)
  - Subseries D: Labor Councils, undated, 1961-1982
    - Building Construction and Trade Councils, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3509-3510)
    - Central, 1961-1982 (Box 31:, Folder 1336-1338)
    - Central Labor Councils, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3511-3515)
    - Central Labor Councils, undated (Box 193)
    - Connecticut
      - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1959-1960 (Box 31:, Folder 1345-1346)
      - Council for the Advancement of Economic Education, 1960-1968 (Box 31:, Folder 1347-1348)
    - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3524)
    - Labor Higher Education Council, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3523)
    - National Council for Senior Citizens, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3525)
    - Northeast AFL-CIO Conference, 1979-1982 (Box 121:, Folder 3526-3529)
    - Other States, 1962-1965 (Box 31:, Folder 1343-1344)
    - Regional Councils, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3516)
    - Regional New England AFL-CIO, 1960-1971 (Box 31:, Folder 1339-1342)
    - State Councils, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3517-3522)
    - Trade union Leadership Council, undated (Box 121:, Folder 3530)
    - Union Label Council, 1965-1967 (Box 31:, Folder 1349)
    - CSLC Executive Board Minutes, 1969-1981 (Box 31:, Folder 1350)
    - CSLC Executive Board attendance records, 1961-1976 (Box 31:, Folder 1351)
  - Subseries E: Conventions, 1958-1990
    - 1958 (Box 32:, Folder 1352)
    - 1958 (Box 123:, Folder 3552)
    - 1959 (Box 32:, Folder 1353)
    - 1959 (Box 123:, Folder 3553)
    - 1960 (Box 32:, Folder 1354-1360)
    - 1960 (Box 123:, Folder 3554)
    - 1961 (Box 32:, Folder 1361-1363)
    - 1961 (Box 123:, Folder 3555)
    - 1962 (Box 32:, Folder 1364-1367)
    - 1963 (Box 32:, Folder 1368)
    - 1963 (Box 123:, Folder 3556-3557)
    - 1964 (Box 32:, Folder 1369-1370)
    - 1964 (Box 123:, Folder 3558)
    - 1965 (Box 32:, Folder 1371)
    - 1965 (Box 123:, Folder 3559)
    - 1967 (Box 32:, Folder 1372)
    - 1967 (Box 123:, Folder 3560)
    - 1968 (Box 123:, Folder 3561)
    - 1969 (Box 123:, Folder 3562-3563)
    - 1970 (Box 123:, Folder 3564-3565)
    - 1972 (Box 123:, Folder 3566-3567)
    - 1975 (Box 123:, Folder 3568)
    - 1976 (Box 123:, Folder 3569)
    - 1977 (Box 123:, Folder 3570)
    - 1979 (Box 123:, Folder 3571)
    - 1980 (Box 32:, Folder 1373-1377)
    - 1980 (Box 123:, Folder 3572)
    - 1981 (Box 32:, Folder 1378)
    - 1981 (Box 123:, Folder 3573-3574)
    - 1983 (Box 123:, Folder 3575)
    - 1987, (27 fl) (Box 190)
    - 1988 (Box 194)
      - Arrangements Committee (Box 194)
      - Assorted papers (Box 194)
      - CLUW Reception for Women of the Year (Box 194)
      - Community Services Committee (Box 194)
      - Convention greetings (Box 194)
      - Education Committee (Box 194)
      - Executive Board and Principals Officers of Affiliates (Box 194)
      - Legislative Committee (Box 194)
      - Materials for Printers (Box 194)
      - Materials ordered for kits (Box 194)
      - Miscellaneous papers (Box 194)
      - Officer's and committee reports (Box 194)
      - Reports (Box 194)
      - Resolutions, (2 fl) (Box 195)
      - Resolutions Committee (Box 195)
      - Rules Committee (Box 195)
      - Speakers and invitations (Box 195)